<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>XxHyde840xX's Choice Chops - Volume Two</name>
    <author>XxHyde840xX/Various</author>
	<url>https://github.com/XxHyde840xX/ChoiceChopsV2</url>
    <description>Another selection of choice items, carefully chopped from their respective mods. An exhaustive list is as follows;
	
	- [Animals And Reskins]
			- There a a good chunk of these, I'm not cross referencing for links. There's far too many and I just want to package them up.
			- This is one of those "I'm trimming my list without trimming my list," inclusions. Sorry folks!
			- I am not the original author of these and all credit goes to the original creators and artists who did the reskins.
			- Obviously incompatible with the original versions, so if you see any of the below animals or skins in your list, yeet 'em!
				
				- Milkrats / Tanuki / Rhodesian Ridgebacks / Pygmy Muffalo / Mamuffalo / Meat Pigs / Domestic Thrumbo / Coldwarg
				- Beefeaters / Muffaloaves / Boomaphants / Insect Meat Reskin / Another Milk Retexture - Re-Bagged! (I hackjobbed this one!)
				- For The (HD) Birds! / The Ugly Duckling / Aurochs / Highland Boomcow / Charming Chihuahuas (Tribute) / Machnorian Chicken
				
			Additional Notes:
				
				- I've removed the glow comp from the Muffaloves. It was a stationary one that the plants use. It's better now.
				- I've also remove the patches for the "A Dog Said" mod as I don't use it. Sorry folks!
				- The Ugly Duckling is a retexture for baby geese. They're called goslings silly. I was confused by this mod too.
				- The Chihuahua is cute as hell and has features listed below. The Machnorian Chicken produces eggs that refine into yayo.
					
					- Life Stages: Experience the growth of chihuahuas from adorable puppies to playful juveniles and chonky adults.
					- Bonding: After forming bonds with your colonists, chihuahuas provide frequent comedic relief (+2 mental buff) and emotional support (+4 mental buff).
					- Healing Licks: Able to heal wounds of nearby colonists and animals.
					- Piercing Bark: Chihuahuas now have a bark ability that can hurt enemies from a range (optional).
					- Digging: Chihuahuas occasionally dig up a range of resources.
				
	- [Geometric Floors, More Floor Coverings, and Royal Carpets by JF]
			- Love the mods, hate the vRAM usage on startup. Seriously, everything needed downscaling. Even the icons.
			- 1024x1024 MAXIMUM for floor textures. Icons down to 128x128 because they were nice.
			- There were around 800-900 textures resized, and it's only around 100-ish MB or so now.
			- Don't want the decor? Deal with it. It's here, and I'm not downscaling it again if my files reset for some reason.
			- The carpets were honestly fine, but they're here too.
			
	- [JD's Simple Switch with Fixed Light Offsets]
			- I liked the switch. The lights were off. They are now where they should be. I didn't even notice the issue.
			- Big thanks to CaptainArbitrary in the RimWorld Discord Server for both alerting me to the problem, and having a fix.
			- All it was was just tweaked textures but it makes all the difference, especially once it was pointed out.
			- Enjoy the power switch! I know I do, the vanilla one is bland as hell.
			
	- [TMC's Gatalog - Select Picks]
			- A few cursed guns from TMC's Gatalog mod. Couldn't pass these up but the rest were kind of...meh. Gotta have some fun though.
			- You get a competition Glock named Big Chungus, a .22LR bolt-action pistol (scoped of course), and a tactical "Space Cowboy" revolver.
			- Not much else to say on this one but enjoy!

      =============================================================================================================================  
	  
	XxHyde840xX - o7
	  
	  =============================================================================================================================
	  |     This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.      |
	  |              To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/                      |
	  |                  or send a letter to Creative Commons, PO Box 1866, Mountain View, CA 94042, USA.                         |
	  =============================================================================================================================
			
	</description>
		<packageId>840.Choice.Chops.V2</packageId>
			<supportedVersions>
				<li>1.4</li>
			</supportedVersions>
    <incompatibleWith>
		<li></li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>Mlie.DogsMate</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid</li>
        <li>VanillaExpanded.VGeneticsE</li>
        <li>sarg.rimbees</li>
        <li>sarg.alphaanimals</li>
		<li>VFME.SimpleTofu</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>