<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>XxHyde840xX's Choice Chops - Volume Two</name>
    <author>XxHyde840xX/Various</author>
	<url>https://github.com/XxHyde840xX/ChoiceChopsV2</url>
    <description>Another selection of choice items, carefully chopped from their respective mods. An exhaustive list is as follows;
	
	- [Animals And Reskins]
			- There a a good chunk of these, I'm not cross referencing for links. There's far too many and I just want to package them up.
			- This is one of those "I'm trimming my list without trimming my list," inclusions. Sorry folks!
			- I am not the original author of these and all credit goes to the original creators and artists who did the reskins.
			- Obviously incompatible with the original versions, so if you see any of the below animals or skins in your list, yeet 'em!
			- I've included some of these in the github release in separate folders in case you just want a couple choice reskins.
				
				- Milkrats / Tanuki / Rhodesian Ridgebacks / Pygmy Muffalo / Mamuffalo / Meat Pigs / Domestic Thrumbo / Coldwarg / Tuffalo
				- Beefeaters / Muffaloaves / Boomaphants / Insect Meat Reskin / Another Milk Retexture - Re-Bagged! (I hackjobbed this one!)
				- For The (HD) Birds! / The Ugly Duckling / Aurochs / Highland Boomcow / Charming Chihuahuas (Tribute) / Machnorian Chicken
				
			Additional Notes:
				
				- I've removed the glow comp from the Muffaloves. It was a stationary one that the plants use. It's better now.
				- I've also remove the patches for the "A Dog Said" mod as I don't use it. Sorry folks!
				- The Ugly Duckling is a retexture for baby geese. They're called goslings silly. I was confused by this mod too.
				- The Chihuahua is cute as hell and has features listed below. The Machnorian Chicken produces eggs that refine into yayo.
					
					- Life Stages: Experience the growth of chihuahuas from adorable puppies to playful juveniles and chonky adults.
					- Bonding: After forming bonds with your colonists, they provide frequent comedic relief (+2 mental buff) and emotional support (+4 mental buff).
					- Healing Licks: Able to heal wounds of nearby colonists and animals.
					- Piercing Bark: Chihuahuas now have a bark ability that can hurt enemies from a range (optional).
					- Digging: Chihuahuas occasionally dig up a range of resources.
				
	- [Geometric Floors, More Floor Coverings, and Royal Carpets by JF]
			- Love the mods, hate the vRAM usage on startup. Seriously, everything needed downscaling. Even the icons.
			- 1024x1024 MAXIMUM for floor textures people. Seriously. Icons are down to 128x128 because they were nice.
			- There were around 800-900 textures resized, nothing over 512x512 now because the vRAM hit was not negligible.
			- Don't want the decor? Deal with it. It's here, and I'm not downscaling it again if my files reset for some reason.
			- The carpets were honestly fine, but they're here too.
			
	- [JD's Simple Switch with Fixed Light Offsets]
			- I liked the switch. The lights were off. They are now where they should be. I didn't even notice the issue.
			- Big thanks to CaptainArbitrary in the RimWorld Discord Server for both alerting me to the problem, and having a fix.
			- All it was was just tweaked textures but it makes all the difference, especially once it was pointed out.
			- Enjoy the power switch! I know I do, the vanilla one is bland as hell.
			
	- [TMC's Gatalog - Select Picks]
			- A few cursed guns from TMC's Gatalog mod. Couldn't pass these up but the rest were kind of...meh. Gotta have some fun though.
			- You get a competition Glock named Big Chungus, a .22LR bolt-action pistol (scoped of course), and a tactical "Space Cowboy" revolver.
			- Not much else to say on this one but enjoy!
			
	- [My Current Mods on Steam]
			- Nothing too crazy here, just a couple mods I have on steam. Figured they might as well be here so I can archive and cleam up my modlist more.
			- You know you were gonna download them anyways. ;) Here's what's compiled:
			
				- Gokusotsu Shougi and Mahjong. Also includes some new snowman textures!
				- An Otter Hat For Otters. Otterly amazing. Also can be made from otters. Otterly troubling...
				- Malay-Style Eaves and Dam Haji.
				- CP's Sentry Turret. Good 'ol P90-in-a-briefcase.
				
	- [Morgante's Post Apocalyptic Pack and Morgante's Furs]
			- Zaljerem was kind enough to provide me with an archive containing some incredible stuff. I wish I could include it all.
			- What I've done with this one is cut out the makeshift weapons, leaving the sweet raider jackets intact.
			- Also left in the gibbet-cage/streetlamp combo building because it was nifty.
			- Morgante's Furs are also included since both reqired the same framework.
			- By the way, you need Oversized Apparel Framework to use the mod now. Sorry, not sorry.
			- I've included these in a separate folder in case you want just this pack standalone.
			
	- [LCM(6) "Zippo" - Armored Gunboat]
			- Let's GO! Now we're getting LIT! You'll have to pardon the pun, the gunboat has FLAMETHROWERS! AHHHHHHH!
			- Was real excited to have another ship, but I don't use Aerocraft Framework so I spun this out from the original mod.
			- All credit goes to Zyszhao on this one, I just yoinked the boat from their "Into The Fire" Vehicle Pack mod.
			- 2 Drivers / 10 Passengers / 15,000Kg of cargo capacity / ARMED TO THE TEETH! / Enjoy!
			- Bonus points for fuelling it with Ferret's Nutrichem System! (Grab it on Steam! I did the textures!)
	
	- [The Woodchuck - A Wood-Powered Pickup Truck]
			- Another one of my translations, both made standalone, and as a Steam translation add-on, now included here, just for you!
			- This one's a bit interesting, one of the first "alternatively-fueled" vehicles no less. Powered by the mighty wood log.
			- Again, I had to clean up the textures a bit to remove the transparent crap left behind by the author, but I got you covered.
			- I love doing these quick translations. It's like 4 lines of text. I'll have more to include so long as the author keeps 'em coming.
			- Bonus points for grabbing Alexis Popcorn's Wooden Pipe Network off of steam and using it to help fuel this silly thing!
			
	- [Jango Unchained]
			- Jango, Jango, Jango. Jango D'Soul. What am I gonna do with you homie? PLEASE STOP USING COMPOVERSIZED AND OTHER UNPERFORMANT .DLL FILES!
			- Seriously. If you ever see this: Your mods are gorgeous, and I appreciate your work, but these .dll files are outdated and SLOW.
			- BEYOND SLOW. 3ms on Dub's Performance Analyzer, and not a single item present on the map.
			- So! What I've done is chopped out a few choice items, making them standalone. This is what's included in this version of Choice Chops from JDS;
			
				- The FROG suit and helmet from MGS 4, worn by the Haven Troopers under Liquid Ocelot's command. The "Gewehr 3" rifle got the chop.
				- Higgs Monaghan Hooded Skull Mask and Rifle. The rifle says "VOID OUT" on the side. 'Nuff Said. Apparently from Death Stranding?
				- Killzone Concept Armor. The "StA25 Vlug" and "StA-3 Light Machine Gun" have been removed. Used to love this game.
				- As payment for your crimes Jango, I've stolen your Ghost Recon Breakpoint Wolves Apparel mod for inclusion as well.
	
	- [The Gunrunners' "Special Reserve" Collection]
			- Ever wanted so many Fallout: New Vegas guns you couldn't possibly ever use them all? Me either, so we're back to the chopping block today.
			- All I've done is curated some of the sweetest, most memorable firearms from Ranger Rick's "Fallout Collaboration Project" New Vegas packs.
			- FNV was a blast and remains one of my favorite games. I am pleased to provide the following fine armaments on behalf of the Gunrunners.
			
				From the FNV Heavy Weapons Collection
					- CZ57 Avenger Minigun / K9000 Cyberdog Gun (FIDO) / Shoulder Mounted Machine Gun				

				From the FNV Sniper Rifles Collection
					- Gobi Campaign Rifle / CoS Silenced Sniper Rifle / Anti-Material Rifle
					
				From the FNV Submachine Guns Collection
					- Silenced .22 SMG / 12.5mm Submachine Gun / "Sleepy Time" 10mm SMG
					
				From the FNV Shotguns Collection
					- Dinner Bell / Lever Action Shotgun / Riot Shotgun
					
				From the FNV Revolvers Collection
					- .357 Magnum "Lucky" / Mysterious Magnum / 556 Pistol
					
				From the FNV Pistols Collection
					- 9mm Pistol / 22mm Silenced Pistol / A Light Shining in The Darkness / Maria / .45 Auto Pistol
					
				From the FNV Lever Action Rifles Collection
					- Abilene Kid BB Gun / La Longue Carabine / Medicine Stick / Brush Gun
					
				From the FNV Assault Rifles Collection
				
					- Bozar / All-American / Automatic Rifle
					
				There is no Fat-Man. Raiders have more than enough BS to throw at us without adding the Fat-Man.
				
	- [Another Milk Retexture - Re-Bagged!]
			- Honestly, I nearly forgot about this one, but there are milk retextures for everything. So. Many. Milk. Retextures.
			- I mashed up two milk retexture mods to include a very Canadian easter-egg. You'll know it when you see it.
			- I apologize for nothing. Open buckets of milk are gross. Thanks MallowYellow and flo.vall for making milk awesome again.

      =============================================================================================================================

	This marks the end of this particular modpack. I've definitely learned alot with this one, everything from fixing authors overwriting
	their own defs in some cases, to proper folder nesting, to downscaling textures en-masse to save on the vRAM hit during startup. I 
	apologize for the large file size on this one, I include .dds textures with all of my stuff so feel free to delete them if you don't
	need them. All in all, I think I did a fairly solid job mashing this all together, and I'm definitely confident in both cracking out
	another version of Choice Chops, as well as some awesome original content in the near future. Until then, stay safe, enjoy the content,
	and make sure not to give those pesky raiders an inch. Or just sit back and run a farm with the umpteen-million animals I've included. I
	won't judge. :)
	  
	XxHyde840xX - o7
	  
	  =============================================================================================================================
	  |     This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.      |
	  |              To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/                      |
	  |                  or send a letter to Creative Commons, PO Box 1866, Mountain View, CA 94042, USA.                         |
	  =============================================================================================================================
			
	</description>
		<packageId>840.Choice.Chops.V2</packageId>
			<supportedVersions>
				<li>1.4</li>
			</supportedVersions>
    <incompatibleWith>
		<li></li>
	</incompatibleWith>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>Vehicle Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3014915404</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaVehiclesExpanded</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Vehicles Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=3014906877</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
            <packageId>bs.oversizedapparel</packageId>
            <displayName>Oversized Apparel Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2630800313</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/bbradson/Oversized-Apparel-Framework</downloadUrl>
        </li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>Mlie.DogsMate</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VFE.Insectoid</li>
        <li>VanillaExpanded.VGeneticsE</li>
        <li>sarg.rimbees</li>
        <li>sarg.alphaanimals</li>
		<li>VFME.SimpleTofu</li>
		<li>bs.oversizedapparel</li>
		<li>zetrith.prepatcher</li>
		<li>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaVehiclesExpanded</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>